Joey Bishop papers
UCLA Library Special Collections
Joey Bishop papers
1967-1976,
bulk 1967-1969
2260
UCLA Library Special Collections
29.0 linear ft. (45 boxes and 11 cartons)
Joey Bishop started his career as a nightclub comedian. He was featured on The Joey Bishop Show and The Joey Bishop Show (late night talk show), and acted in various motion pictures, including Ocean's Eleven and Valley of the Dolls. In the 1960s and 1970s, he also performed regularly with the Rat Pack. The collection consists largely of records pertaining to The Joey Bishop Show (late night talk show) and is made up of guest research files, guest contracts, weekly lineups, and financial records. Also included in the collection are a small number of scripts representing Bishop's other television projects.
Bishop, Joey
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Portions of the Guest Contracts are restricted. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed in writing to the UCLA Library Special Collections.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7680379
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Nora Garibotti, 2014 and 2015.
Biography/History
Joseph Abraham Gottlieb, later changed to Joey Bishop, was born February 3, 1918 (some sources say 1919) in Bronx, New York. Bishop established himself as a nightclub comedian by the early 1950s, and was nicknamed The Frown Prince of Comedy for his cynical demeanor. It was during this time that he caught the attention of Frank Sinatra, who hired him as his opening act. Bishop started his television career performing standup comedy on the Cavalcade of Stars. He regularly appeared on the game show Keep Talking, and as a guest host for Jack Paar and Johnny Carson on the Tonight Show. In the 1960s, Bishop earned a spot in the Rat Pack, a group of entertainers comprising Frank Sinatra, Dean Martin, Sammy Davis, Jr., and Peter Lawford, who performed live in Las Vegas, Miami, Atlantic City, and Palm Springs.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of comedian and actor Joey Bishop. The bulk of materials are related to the Joey Bishop Show (late night talk show) and include research files pertaining guests and potential guests, weekly line-ups, financial records, and guest contracts. Additionally there are a small number of scripts representing Bishop's appearances on other television programs. Notably absent are materials related to Bishop's film career and connection with the Rat Pack.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Joey Bishop Show Records
Television Projects
Bishop, Joey; Actors--United States--Archives.; Comedians-United States-Archives.
Container List
- Joey Bishop Show Records.
  Restrictions on Access
  Guest contract files are restricted and may be unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed in writing to the UCLA Library Special Collections.
  Scope and Content
  The series consist of materials documenting the production of the Joey Bishop Show talk show. The series is arranged into four subseries: 1. Guest research files; 2. Guest contracts; 3. Weekly lineups; 4. Financial records.
  The Guest Research files include information about many of the guests (and potential guests) that appeared on the Joey Bishop talk show and may contain one or more of the following: one-page research synopsis, head shots, clippings, and publicity ephemera. The files are arranged alphabetically by last and/or group name.
  The Weekly Lineup files may include rundowns, monologue material, notes/talking points related to guests, and cue cards. The files are arranged chronologically.
  The Financial records comprise six ledgers: two ledgers labelled Joey Bishop Productions and four ledgers labelled accounts payable.
  The Guest Contracts are Standard AFTRA Engagement Contracts for talent who appeared on the show. The contracts are arranged in a reverse chronological order by what appears to be the weekly air dates. The Guest Contracts are restricted and require advanced notice for use.
  - Financial Records.
    - Accounts Payable Ledger., 1969. (Box 47)
    - Accounts Payable Ledger., 1967. (Box 47)
    - Accounts Payable Ledger., 1968. (Box 48)
    - Accounts Payable Ledger., 1969. (Box 48)
    - General Ledger labeled Joey Bishop Productions Acct #2., Fiscal year end 1967 Nov 30 - 1968. (Box 49)
    - General Ledger labeled Joey Bishop Productions Acct #2., Fiscal year end 1969 Nov 30 - 1970. (Box 50)
  - Guest Contracts., 1967 April - December 1969.
    - Contracts weeks of 1967 April 17- July 10,. (Box 60)
      Portions of the contents of the files are restricted and may be unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed in writing to the UCLA Library Special Collections.
    - Contracts weeks of 1967 July 17 - Oct 23. (Box 59)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Portions of the contents of this folder are restricted and may be unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed in writing to the UCLA Library Special Collections.
    - Contracts weeks of Oct 30, 1967 - Jan 29, 1968., 1968-1969. (Box 58)
    - Contracts weeks of 1968 Feb 5 - May 20. (Box 57)
    - Contracts weeks of 1968 May 27 - Sep 23. (Box 56)
    - Contracts weeks of 1968 Sep 30 - Dec 30.
    - Contracts weeks of 1969 Jan 6 - Mar 31. (Box 54)
    - Contracts Week of 1969 April 7 - June 30. (Box 53)
    - Contracts weeks of 1969 Sept 29 - July 7. (Box 52)
    - Contracts weeks of 1969 Oct 6- Dec 22. (Box 51)
  - Guest Research Files.
    - Mystery Guests., ca. 1968. (Box 1)
    - A., ca. 1967-1968. (Box 1)
    - Abernathy, Dr. Ralph., 1969 Oct. (Box 1)
    - Adderly, Cannonball., ca. 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Alan, Don., 1968 Oct-Dec. (Box 1)
    - Alberghetti, Anna Maria., ca.1967, 1969. (Box 1)
    - Albert, Eddie., ca. 1969. (Box 1)
    - Albertson, Jack., 1969 Apr. (Box 1)
    - Alcindor, Lew and Warren, Mike., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Lou., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Allen, Chris & Peter., 1969. (Box 1)
    - Allen, George., 1969. (Box 1)
    - Allen, Steve & Meadows, Jane., 1969. (Box 1)
    - Almeida, Laurindo., 1969 Aug - Dec. (Box 1)
    - American Breed., 1968 Feb. (Box 1)
    - Ames, Ed., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Ames, Nancy., 1967-1969. (Box 1)
    - Amory, Cleveland., 1968 Aug-Nov. (Box 1)
    - Amsterdam, Morey., 1969 Dec. (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Bill., 1969 Nov. (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Lynn., 1969 Nov and Aug. (Box 1)
    - Andress, Ursula., 1969 June. (Box 1)
    - Andretti, Mario., 1969 June. (Box 1)
    - Andrews Sisters., 1968. (Box 1)
    - Anjoan., 1969. (Box 1)
    - Anka, Paul., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Antes, Jerry., 1968 July. (Box 1)
    - The Apollas., 1969 April and July. (Box 1)
    - Apollo 10 Astronauts - Stafford, Cernan, and Young., 1969. (Box 1)
    - Appel, Cantor Sam., undated. (Box 1)
    - Archer, George., 1969 April. (Box 1)
    - Arden, Tony., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Argo, Judy., 1969 June. (Box 1)
    - Arlen, David., 1969 Sep. (Box 1)
    - Armed Forces., undated. (Box 1)
    - Art & Honey., 1969 Sep-Oct. (Box 1)
    - Arthur, Maureen., 1969 Jul. (Box 1)
    - Arthur, Maureen., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Ash, Glen., 1969. (Box 1)
    - The Association., 1968-1969. (Box 1)
    - Atkins, Chet., 1968 Dec. (Box 1)
    - Aumont, Jean Pierre., 1968 Oct. (Box 1)
    - Avalon, Frankie., 1967-1969. (Box 1)
    - Aznavour, Charles., undated. (Box 1)
    - B., 1967-1969. (Box 1)
    - Bacharach, Burt., 1968. (Box 2)
    - Backus, Jim., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Backwards (Professor Backwards)., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Baez, Joan., 1967, 1969. (Box 2)
    - Bailey, F. Lee., 1969 Sep. (Box 2)
    - Bailey, Pearl. (Box 2)
    - Baja Marimba Band., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Banks, Dr. Murray., undated. (Box 2)
    - Barbour, John., 1968 Sep. (Box 2)
    - Barbutti, Pete., 1968-1969. (Box 2)
    - Barnum, Captain Harvey, USMC., 1968 Jan. (Box 2)
    - Baron, Sandy., 1969 April. (Box 2)
    - Barr, Leonard., 1968-1969. (Box 2)
    - Barrett, Susan., 1968. (Box 2)
    - Barry, Dave., undated. (Box 2)
    - Barry, Ken., 1969 June-July. (Box 2)
    - Bassey, Shirley., 1968 April. (Box 2)
    - Baxter, Anne., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Baylos, Gene., 1968-1969. (Box 2)
    - Bayth, Senator Birch., 1968. (Box 2)
    - Beach Boys, The., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Bearns, Robert., 1968 April. (Box 2)
    - Bedford, Duchess of., 1968 Nov 5. (Box 2)
    - Bee, Molly., 1968. (Box 2)
    - Begley, Ed., 1968. (Box 2)
    - Belland and Sommerville., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Bennett, Tony., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Benny, Jack., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Benton, Brook., undated. (Box 2)
    - Bergen, Candice., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Bergen, Edgar., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Bergen, Polly., 1968. (Box 2)
    - Berger, Senta., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Berkeley, Busby., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Berle, Milton., 1969. (Box 2)
    - Berman, Shelly., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Berry, Albert T.., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Berry, Ken., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Bets, Carl., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Bill & Quinn., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Bishop, Rummy (with Anne Vance)., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Blackstone, Harry Jr.., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Blair, Sally., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Blodgett, Michael., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Blomen, Henning A.., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Blondell, Joan., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Blossoms, The., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Blyth, Ann., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Bocar, Poupee., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Boone, Pat., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Borge, Victor., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Borgine, Ernest., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Bornstein, Arthur., undated. (Box 3)
    - Bossa Rio., undated. (Box 3)
    - Boutelle, Paul., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Bow, Simmy., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Boxley and Marie., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Boyce and Heart., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Boyd, Secretary Alan S.., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Boyd, Stephen., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Bradley, General Omar N.., 1967. (Box 3)
    - Breck, Peter., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Brill, Marty., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Brothers Castro., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Brothers James., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Brown, Helen Gurley., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Brown, James., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Brown, Jim., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Bruno, Victor., 1969. (Box 3)
    - The Buckinghams., undated. (Box 3)
    - Buffalo Springfield., undated. (Box 3)
    - Bulifant, Joyce., 1967. (Box 3)
    - Burgandy Street Singers., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Burke, Michelle., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Burke, Solomon., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Burnett, Carol., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Burns, George., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Burns, Jack., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Burns, Susan., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Burnstein, Mike., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Butler, Jerry., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Buttons, Red., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Buttram, Pat., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Byers, Brenda., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Byington, Spring., 1969. (Box 3)
    - Byner, John., 1968. (Box 3)
    - Byrd, Charlie., 1968. (Box 3)
    - the Byrds., undated. (Box 3)
    - C., undated. (Box 4)
    - Caiden, Martin., undated. (Box 4)
    - Caine, Michael., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Callas, Charlie., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Campbell, Glen., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Cantrell, Lana., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Captain Kangaroo., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Carazini., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Carey, Macdonald., undated. (Box 4)
    - Carey, Michele., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Cargill, Henson., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Carlin, George., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Carlson, Cathy., 1969. (Box 4)
    - The Carlssons., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Carmen., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Carne, Judy., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Carney, Art., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Carr, Vikki., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Carrol, Diahann., undated. (Box 4)
    - Carter, Jack., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Carter, Mel., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Casey, Bernie., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Cash, Johnny., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Casper, Billy., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Cassavetes Falk, and Gazzara., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Cassavetes, John., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Casserole Caterers., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Cassidy, Jack., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Castle, Jo Ann., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Chad & Jeremy., 1967. (Box 4)
    - Channing, Carol., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Charles, Ray & Group., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Charney, Suzanne., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Chase, Dr. Loriene., 1969. (Box 4)
    - The Checkmates, Ltd., undated. (Box 4)
    - Cherry, Don., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Christen, Nadia., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Christie, Lou., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Clark, Attorney General Ramsey., 1968. (Box 4)
    - Clark, Dick., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Clark, Roy., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Clarke, Jackie., 1969. (Box 4)
    - Clary, Robert., no date. (Box 4)
    - The Classics IV., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Clooney, Rosemary., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Cochran, Wayne., no date. (Box 5)
    - Cocker, Joe., no date. (Box 5)
    - Cohen, Myron., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Collins Kids., undated. (Box 5)
    - Collins, Judy., undated. (Box 5)
    - Collins, Mary Lou., undated. (Box 5)
    - Colvin & Wilder., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Condos, Melodye., 1968. (Box 5)
    - The Congregation., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Conigliaro, Tony., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Connors, Chuck., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Connors, Michael., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Conot, Robert., 1967. (Box 5)
    - Conrad, Bob., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Contino, Dick., undated. (Box 5)
    - Cooper, Dame Gladys., undated. (Box 5)
    - Cooper, Pat., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Copeland, Alan., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Corey, Prof. Irwin., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Costa, Mary., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Costello, Diosa., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Cotton, Joseph., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Count Basie., 1967. (Box 5)
    - Cousteau, Jacques., 1969. (Box 5)
    - The Cowsills., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Crawford, Broderick., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Crenna, Richard., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Cristal, Linda., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Crosby, Bing and Kathryn., 1967. (Box 5)
    - Crosby, Chris., 1967. (Box 5)
    - Crosby, Gary., 1967. (Box 5)
    - Crosby, Norm., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Crosby, Phil., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Cugat, Xavier & Charo., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Culp, Robert., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Curtis, Tony., 1969. (Box 5)
    - D., undated. (Box 5)
    - Dahl, Arlene., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Dailey, Dan., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Damita Jo., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Dana, Bill., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Dana, Vic., 1968. (Box 5)
    - Dangerfield, Rodney., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Daniels, Billy., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Darin, Bobby., 1969. (Box 5)
    - Darren, James., 1967. (Box 6)
    - Darrow, Henry., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Daryll, Tony., 1968. (Box 6)
    - David & Kim., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Davis & Reese., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Bette., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Don., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Gwen., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Sammy., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Dawson, Richard., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Day, Dennis., 1968. (Box 6)
    - De Carlo, Yvonne., 1968. (Box 6)
    - De Leon, Jack., 1968. (Box 6)
    - De Luise, Dom., undated. (Box 6)
    - De Shannon, Jackie., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Dean, Jimmy., 1969. (Box 6)
    - The Dells., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Diamond, Neil., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Diamond, Selma., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Dickinson, Angie., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Diller, Phyllis., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Dino, Desi & Billy., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Dors, Diana., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Douglas, Kirk., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Doyle, Bobby., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Drake, Allan., no date. (Box 6)
    - Drake, Debbie., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Draper, Rusty., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Dresser, Lee., 1969. (Box 6)
    - D'Rone, Frank., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Drysdale, Don., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Duke, Patty., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Dunn, Elaine., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Dunn, Michael., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Durante, Jimmy., 1969. (Box 6)
    - E., undated. (Box 6)
    - Eastwood, Clint., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Eckstine, Billy., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Eden, Barbara., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Eisenmann, Chuck., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Ellington, Duke., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Elliot, Lu., 1968. (Box 6)
    - Eric Burdon and the Animals., undated. (Box 3)
    - Ettinger, Robert C.W.., 1967. (Box 6)
    - Evans, Dame Edith., undated. (Box 6)
    - Everly Bros.., undated. (Box 6)
    - F., undated. (Box 7)
    - The Fabulous Exciters., 1969. (Box 6)
    - Falana, Lola., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fanelli, Frank., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Faye, Frances., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Ferrare, Cristina., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Ferrer, Jose., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Ferro, Talya., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Field, Sally., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fields, Leon., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fields, Totie., 1969. (Box 7)
    - The Fifth Dimension., undated. (Box 7)
    - Finn, Fred, & Mickie., 1969. (Box 7)
    - The First Edition., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Fisher & Marks., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fisher, Eddie., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Fisher, Stan., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Fitzgerald, Ella., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Flag, Fannie., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fleming, Peggy., 1969. (Box 7)
    - The Flying Burrito Bros.., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Foch, Nina., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Foley, Brian., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fonda, Henry., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Fonda, Jane., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Fonda, Peter., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Ford & Hines., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Forsythe, John., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Foster, Phil., 1969. (Box 7)
    - The Four King Cousins., 1969. (Box 7)
    - The Four Lads., 1967. (Box 7)
    - The Four Seasons., no date. (Box 7)
    - The Four Step Brothers., 1969. (Box 21)
    - The Four Tops., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Foxx, Redd., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Franchi, Sergio., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Francis, Anne., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Francis, Connie., 1967. (Box 7)
    - Franciscus, James., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Franklin, Aretha., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Frazier, Hal., 1968. (Box 7)
    - Frazier, Joe., 1969. (Box 7)
    - French, Leigh., 1969. (Box 7)
    - The Freshman Four., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Friends of Distinction., 1969. (Box 7)
    - Frushay, Ray., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Frye, David., 1968. (Box 8)
    - G., undated. (Box 8)
    - Gabor, Eva., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gabor, Zsa Zsa., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gabriel, Roman., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Galon, Gigi., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Garner, Erroll., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Garner, James., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Garrett, Kelly., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Garson, Greer., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gary, John., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gavin, John., 1967. (Box 8)
    - Gaye, Marvin., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gayle, Jackie., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Gazzara, Ben., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Geezinslaw Brothers., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gemini Twins., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Gentry, Bobbie., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gernreich, Rudi., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Ghostley, Alice., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gibbs, Georgia., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Gibson, Bob., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Gibson, Henry., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gilbert, Paul., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gillespie, Dizzy., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Gilliam, Stu., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Giovanni, Dr.., 1968. (Box 8)
    - The Girls from Bahia., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Gish, Lillian., 1969. (Box 8)
    - The Going Thing., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Goldsboro, Bobby., 1968. (Box 8)
    - Golonka, Arlene., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gonzales, Pancho., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Goodman, Linda., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Don and the Goodtimes., undated. (Box 8)
    - Gordon, Kelly., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gordon, Ruth., 1969. (Box 8)
    - Gore, Leslie., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Gorshin, Frank., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Gould, Sid., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Goulet, Robert., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Graham, Billy., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Graham, Virginia., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Graham, Virginia., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Granatelli, Andy., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Granger, Gerri., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Grant, Earl., 1969. (Box 9)
    - The Grass Roots., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Graves, Peter., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Graziano, Rocky., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Greaves, R.B.., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Greco, Buddy., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Greenbaum, Everett., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Greene, Lorne., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Greenwald, Ken., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Griffin, Bessie., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Griffin, Grant., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Griffith, Andy., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Grimes, Tammy., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Guy and David., 1968. (Box 9)
    - H., 1968-1969. (Box 9)
    - Hackett, Buddy., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Hackson, Mahalia., 1968. (Box 11)
    - The Hagers., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Halstead, Fred., 1968. (Box 9)
    - Hampton, Lionel., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Handelman, Stanley Myron., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hanlon, Brendan., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Harkness Ballet., 1969. (Box 9)
    - Harlem Globetrotters., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Harpers Bizarre., undated. (Box 10)
    - Harris, Julie., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Harris, Richard., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Harris, Senator Fred R.., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Harrison, Noel., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Harryman, Claude., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Hart, Diane., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hart, Kate., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hartford, John., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Harvey, Laurence., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Hastings, Ray., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hay, Alexander., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Haynes, Lloyd., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hayward, Susan., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Heller, Barbara., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Henderson, Florence., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hendra & Ullett., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Henry, Pat., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Herman, Woody., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Heywood, Anne., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hines, Earl "Fatha"., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Hines, Hines & Dad., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Hirt, Al., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Ho, Don., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Holden, William., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Holiday, Ron & Joy., 1968. (Box 10)
    - The Hollies., 1967. (Box 10)
    - Homer & Jethro., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Honey, Ltd.., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hope, Bob., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Houston, David., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Houston, Thelma., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Howes, Sally Ann., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Huebner, Louise., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hughes, Rhetta & The Abstractions., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H.., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Hunter, Tab., 1969. (Box 10)
    - Husky, Ferlin., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Husmann, Ron., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Hussey, Olivia & Whiting, Leonard., 1968. (Box 10)
    - Huston, John., 1969. (Box 10)
    - I J K., 1967-1968. (Box 10)
    - Ian & Sylvia., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Ian, Janis., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Ice Capades., 1969. (Box 11)
    - The Illegitimate Theatre., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Imperials, Anthony and The., 1968. (Box 11)
    - The Impressions., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Ingels, Marty., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Inner Dialogue., 1969. (Box 11)
    - The Irish Rovers., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jackson, Jesse., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Jackson, Reggie., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jackson, Wanda., undated. (Box 11)
    - James, Sonny., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Janssen, David., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jay & the Techniques (folder 1 of 2)., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Jay & the Techniques (folder 2 of 2) (45 rpm phonograph records).
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      RESTRICTED ACCESS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - Jeffreys, Anne., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Jeffries, Fran., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jennifer., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jennings, Waylon., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jensen, Dick Group., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jessel, George., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jillson, Joyce., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Joffrey Ballet., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Johnson, Bayn., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jones, Carolyn., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jones, Deacon (David)., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Jones, Dean., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Jones, George., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jones, Jack., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Jones, January., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Jones, Shirley., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Jordan, Will., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Kabuki Dancers., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Kahane, Jackie., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Kalil and Taylor., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Kanter, Hal., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Karate Team., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Kasandra., 1968. (Box 11)
    - Kashi, Aliza., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Kauffeld, Greetje., 1969. (Box 11)
    - Kaye, Georgie., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kazan, Lainie., 1969. (Box 12)